aboutdesk.com 2006-05-07

# Privacy Policies - AboutDesk

AboutDesk works in affiliation with online merchants. All prices displayed on this site are subject to change without notice. Although we do our best to keep all links up to date and valid on a daily basis, We cannot guarantee the accuracy of links and special offers displayed. AboutDesk is not responsible for any products ordered from our affiliate merchants and we cannot be held responsible for any actions of our affiliated merchants. 

**PRIVACY STATEMENT:**  
AboutDesk respects the privacy of every individual who visits AboutDesk. This Privacy Statement describes the information collected and how it will be used. 

**PERSONAL INFORMATION:**  
AboutDesk will not collect or retain any personal information such as your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address, unless you choose to provide it. If you provide this information, AboutDesk will only use it for our own information. We will not sell or otherwise divulge the information to 3rd parties. 

**WEB LOGS:**  
AboutDesk collects certain technical information when you visit our website. For example, the domain name from which you accessed our site, the pages visited and the date and time you accessed our site are analyzed to make our site more useful to visitors. But, we only use IP addresses and these are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**COOKIES:**  
No cookies are used at AboutDesk. 

**LINKS TO MERCHANT SITES:**  
AboutDesk contains links to merchant sites. Be aware that AboutDesk is not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by AboutDesk. 

[an error occurred while processing this directive] 

Fresh Air from WHYY , May 3, 2006 · Rock critic Ken Tucker reviews Living with War , a new CD by Neil Young that includes the song "Let's Impeach the President." He posted the entire album on his website last week for free. It's now on sale as a CD.

A $39 million children's fantasy movie largely filmed in Central Otago four years ago has screened in the United States to lukewarm reviews.

[The New & Improved MyHotSauces.Com Website Opens To Rave Reviews (PR Web)](http://us.rd.yahoo.com/dailynews/rss/search/Website+reviews/SIG=11oqrj27u/*http%3A//www.prweb.com/releases/2006/5/prweb374298.htm)  
MyHotSauces.Com opens it's new and improved website shopping cart to big numbers and great response. (PRWEB May 3, 2006) Trackback URI: http://www.prweb.com/dingpr.php/WmV0YS1TaW5nLUluc2UtSG9yci1IYWxmLVplcm8=

[CyberSignal.org | Blog Software | Blog | Blogging | Free Blog (CyberSignal)](http://us.rd.yahoo.com/dailynews/rss/search/Website+reviews/SIG=18l0o236u/*http%3A//www.cybersignal.org/Blog-Software.html?additionalParams=dmxargs=03u3hs9yoajmUOOzCDRBATT9aXIC4KYuEXPpcC4jAbJWhbYymO-3xREKpm5pFp6Z0sPjXE5k3eGDlijTvx07F-c_ibzeGVkW4-miJj4EZ6hH_tv0yyG7y_DbQgADBSqrChKa_WnzkLtW_VVaoOAC5R6x0NWgi2VyU9HNJlbkBfsS1ZAWXdgoPDlpGmMm2jscmkL-XIwM46)  
Want Blog Code? Create a custom poll and export the code for free. Ask your readers anything. www.vizu.com Blog Software Easy web software to create and manage your small business website. Includes drag and drop simplicity, WYSIWYG, extensive content, e-commerce, and no HTML knowledge required.
